{"FormName":"Chiro Form","FormId":"35","PatientId":null,"DoctorId":null,"DoctorLocationId":null,"AppointmentId":null,"DateCompleted":null,"DateUpdated":null,"FormSelectedTemplateID":-1,"FormSections":[{"SectionName":"Basic Info","SectionId":"9","SectionSelectedTemplateID":-1,"SectionQuestions":[{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"431","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Claimant Name","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"701","AnswerText":"Dan Left Shoulder","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"432","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Claim Number","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"702","AnswerText":"12345","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"433","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"Date","QuestionText":"Today''s Date","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"703","AnswerText":"9/29/2016 10:00:00 PM","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"434","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"Date","QuestionText":"Date of Birth","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"704","AnswerText":"10/30/2018 11:00:00 PM","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"435","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Age","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"705","AnswerText":"11","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"442","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Height","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"443","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Weight","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"444","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Please describe which photo ID was presented.","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"444","OptionText":"New York State Driver's License","OptionId":"505","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"444","OptionText":"Passport","OptionId":"506","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"444","OptionText":"Employment Card","OptionId":"507","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"444","OptionText":"Photo ID","OptionId":"508","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"445","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"Radio","QuestionText":"Right-handed or left-handed?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"706","AnswerText":"Right","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"445","OptionText":"Right","OptionId":"509","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":true},{"ParentQuestionId":"445","OptionText":"Left","OptionId":"510","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"446","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Hair color","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"446","OptionText":"brown","OptionId":"511","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"446","OptionText":"dark brown","OptionId":"512","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"446","OptionText":"light brown","OptionId":"513","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"446","OptionText":"black","OptionId":"514","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"446","OptionText":"blonde","OptionId":"515","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"446","OptionText":"red","OptionId":"516","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"446","OptionText":"gray","OptionId":"517","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"446","OptionText":"no hair","OptionId":"518","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"447","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Eye color","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"447","OptionText":"hazel","OptionId":"519","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"447","OptionText":"green","OptionId":"520","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"447","OptionText":"blue","OptionId":"521","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"447","OptionText":"brown","OptionId":"522","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"447","OptionText":"gray","OptionId":"523","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"448","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Photo of claimant","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"449","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Vendor number","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"9","QuestionId":"450","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"Date","QuestionText":"Date of Accident","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null}]},{"SectionName":"Accident Info","SectionId":"10","SectionSelectedTemplateID":-1,"SectionQuestions":[{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"460","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"Date","QuestionText":"Date of Accident","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"707","AnswerText":"11/29/2019 11:00:00 PM","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"461","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"Radio","QuestionText":"Type of Accident","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"461","OptionText":"motor vehicle accident","OptionId":"546","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"461","OptionText":"worker's comp","OptionId":"547","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"461","OptionText":"Other","OptionId":"548","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":true}]},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"672","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"Check","QuestionText":"Do you have a history of any serious illnesses including:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"672","OptionText":"No history of illness","OptionId":"682","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"672","OptionText":"High Blood Pressure","OptionId":"683","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":true},{"ParentQuestionId":"672","OptionText":"Asthma","OptionId":"684","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"672","OptionText":"Diabetes","OptionId":"685","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"672","OptionText":"Cancer","OptionId":"686","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"672","OptionText":"Arthritis","OptionId":"687","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"672","OptionText":"Other","OptionId":"688","ConditionTriggerId":"270","Chosen":true}]},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"673","QuestionParentId":"672","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Describe:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"270","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"711","AnswerText":"Left shoulder sprain","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"674","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Are you currently taking any medication?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"674","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"271","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"674","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"675","QuestionParentId":"674","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Type of medication:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"271","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"676","QuestionParentId":"674","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Dosage and frequency:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"271","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"677","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Are you allergic to any medications?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"677","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"272","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"677","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"678","QuestionParentId":"677","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Type of medication:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"272","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"679","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Have you had any surgery in the past (NOT RELATED TO THIS ACCIDENT)","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"679","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"273","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"679","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"680","QuestionParentId":"679","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Type of surgery:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"273","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"681","QuestionParentId":"679","QuestionType":"Date","QuestionText":"Date of surgery:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"273","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"682","QuestionParentId":"679","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Reason for surgery:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"273","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"683","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"BodyParts","QuestionText":"What are your current complaints as a result of the accident?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"No initial complaints","OptionId":"549","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Headaches","OptionId":"550","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Neck ","OptionId":"551","ConditionTriggerId":"274","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Mid Back","OptionId":"552","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Low Back","OptionId":"553","ConditionTriggerId":"275","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Right Shoulder","OptionId":"554","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Left Shoulder","OptionId":"555","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Right Elbow","OptionId":"556","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Left Elbow","OptionId":"557","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Right Wrist","OptionId":"558","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Left Wrist","OptionId":"559","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Right Hand","OptionId":"560","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Left Hand","OptionId":"561","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Right Hip","OptionId":"562","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Left Hip","OptionId":"563","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Right Knee","OptionId":"564","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Left Knee","OptionId":"565","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Right Ankle","OptionId":"566","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Left Ankle","OptionId":"567","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Right Foot","OptionId":"568","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Left Foot","OptionId":"569","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"683","OptionText":"Other (Please list)","OptionId":"570","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"684","QuestionParentId":"683","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Does your neck pain radiate to your arms or hands?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"274","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"684","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"684","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"685","QuestionParentId":"683","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Does your back pain radiate to your arms or hands?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"275","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"685","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"685","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"686","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Have you ever had any of the above complaints prior to the accident?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"686","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"276","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"686","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"10","QuestionId":"687","QuestionParentId":"686","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Please list","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"276","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null}]},{"SectionName":"History","SectionId":"11","SectionSelectedTemplateID":-1,"SectionQuestions":[{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"688","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Were you employed at the time of the accident?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"688","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"277","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"688","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"689","QuestionParentId":"688","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"What was your occupation?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"277","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"715","AnswerText":"Factory","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"690","QuestionParentId":"688","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Your duties included:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"277","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"691","QuestionParentId":"688","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Did you miss any time from work as a result of the accident?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"277","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"691","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"278","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"691","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"692","QuestionParentId":"691","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"How much time from work did you miss? (Days/Weeks/Months)","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"278","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"717","AnswerText":"4","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"693","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Are you currently working?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"693","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"280","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"693","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"279","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"694","QuestionParentId":"693","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Explain why:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"279","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"695","QuestionParentId":"693","QuestionType":"Radio","QuestionText":"Are you working full-time or part-time?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"280","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"695","OptionText":"Full Time","OptionId":"689","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"695","OptionText":"Part Time","OptionId":"690","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":true}]},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"696","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"How much walking do you perform per day?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"697","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"How much sitting do you do per day?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"698","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"How much standing do you do per day?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"699","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Do you do any climbing (stairs/ladders)","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"699","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"699","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"700","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Do you perform household chores, cooking, cleaning, etc?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"700","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"700","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"701","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"YesNo","QuestionText":"Do you perform any heavy lifting?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":[{"ParentQuestionId":"701","OptionText":"Yes","OptionId":"7","ConditionTriggerId":"281","Chosen":false},{"ParentQuestionId":"701","OptionText":"No","OptionId":"8","ConditionTriggerId":"","Chosen":false}]},{"SectionId":"11","QuestionId":"702","QuestionParentId":"701","QuestionType":"TextInput","QuestionText":"Explain:","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"281","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":true,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null}]},{"SectionName":"Basic Info","SectionId":"12","SectionSelectedTemplateID":-1,"SectionQuestions":[{"SectionId":"12","QuestionId":"719","QuestionParentId":"0","QuestionType":"Radio","QuestionText":"What is your gender?","QuestionKeyboardType":null,"ParentConditionTriggerId":"","ActiveTriggerId":null,"IsConditional":false,"AnswerId":"","AnswerText":"","IsAnswered":false,"IsEnabled":false,"AnswerOptionIndex":null,"QuestionOptions":null}]}]}